

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER · JAVA DEVELOPER

Ashtown, Dublin - Ireland

🛘 (+353) 83 376 9878 | 🗷 anderson.frsoares@catolica.edu.br | 🌴 andersonfls.github.io/portifolioDev/ | 🖸 Andersonfls | 🛅 andersonfr

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

## Summary.

Developer focused on web systems with 5+ years of experience working with Java. Known to possess strong technical knowledge to deliver solid systems.

In the past 2 years i've been working as a Fullstack developer, with Angular 4+, JavaScript, Css and HTML for the frontend and JAVA, Spring Boot, Maven, Git and others for the backend.

Continued education has allowed me to stay ahead of the curve and deliver exceptional work to each employer I've worked for.

# Work Experience\_

#### **Independent Software Developer**

Brasilia, Brazil

**FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 

Jul. 2017 - PRESENT

- Independent software developer, working on projects of all sizes.
- Responsible for the construction of a module for communication and sending data to the Federal Revenue Service, for a private pension institute with more than 100 thousand members.
- · Responsible for integrating the company's internal systems (data processing), working with Spring bath for process management.
- Working with JavaScript, Css, Xhtml and JSF for the front-end.
- Working with Java, Spring boot, Spring batch, Maven, WebServices, JasperReport, Svn, Jboss, Junit and Oracle for the back-end.

Objetiva I.T

Brasilia, Brazil

JAVA DEVELOPER (SOFTWARE: FINANCIAL SOFTWARE FOR CREDIT MANAGEMENT)

Oct. 2015 - May. 2017

- · High complexity software, responsible for managing clients, negotiate debts, manage customer portfolios, generate statistics
- Responsible for development of the Api, with Spring boot and Spring Security and creating new features.
- Working with Java, JSF, Hibernate, JasperReport, Git, Junit, Oracle, SQL, Anguar 2

Objetiva I.T Brasilia, Brazil

JAVA DEVELOPER (SOFTWARE: HEALTH SERVICES MANAGEMENT)

Oct. 2015 - May. 2017

- Developer of the project in a Public Institution (TCU) I mainly work on creating new functionalities and evolution of existing functionalities.
- · Responsible for managing all health system of the public institution, including users, queries, integration's with other systems
- Working with Java, Spring boot, Struts 2, MVC, EJB, Maven, WebServices, JasperReport, Git, Jboss, Junit, Oracle, SQL, Design Pattern.

### Ministério Público do Trabalho

Brasilia, Brazil
Oct. 2015 - May. 2017

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

- Responsible for developing front-end pages in JSF, Html, Css.
- Responsible for monitoring the management software process.
- Working with Java, Spring boot, Struts 2, MVC, EJB, Maven, WebServices, JasperReport, Git, Jboss, Junit, Oracle, SQL, Design Pattern.

Grupo Empreza Brasilia, Brazil

**BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE ANALYST** 

Apr. 2013, Oct. 2013

- · Responsible for development of Reports and Dashboards in excel
- Responsible for the maintenance of the WEB systems of the company, data processing, integration with Excel macros.

### **Education**

#### UCB - Universidade Católica de Brasília

Brasilia, Brazil

ASSOCIATE DEGREE IN SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND DEVELOPMENT

Jan. 2012 - Exp. Dez. 2015

• Focus on Development of web systems with java and agile methods

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **UCB - Universidade Católica and IBM**

Brasilia, Brazil

BASIC OF JCL MAINFRAME, BASIC OF COBOL

Jan. 2014 - Dez. 2014

- · Course Offered by IBM when i have the opportunity to learn how the mainframe works and make some projects with Mainframe
- · Course Offered by IBM when i have the opportunity to learn Cobol and make some codes to run into a Mainframe